A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor Thomas B. Stanley, 1954-1958
Library of Virginia
- Series I: State Government, 1954-1958., Extent: 19.6 cu. ft. (56 boxes). (Box Boxes 1-56)
  - Motor Vehicles, Division of, Division of Report of Gasoline Tax Collector (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Motor Vehicles, Division of, Division of Gasoline Collection comparison (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Motor Vehicles, Division of, Division of Recommendations (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Personnel, Division of, Director, 1954-1955 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Personnel, Division of, Director, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Personnel, Division of, Director, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Personnel, Division of, Executive Orders, 1954-1957 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Personnel, Division of, Personnel handbook (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Southern Business and Industry Conference (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - State Compensation Board (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - State Police, Dept. of, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - State Police, Dept. of, 1955 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - State Police, Dept. of, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - State Police, Dept. of, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - State Police, Dept. of, Dept. of Public Safety, W.L. Groth (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - State Police, Dept. of, Dept. of Reports (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - State Police, Dept. of, Dept. of Speed Law (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - State Police, Dept. of, Recommendations (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Statutory Research and Drafting, Division of (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Taxation, Dept. of, Commissioner (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Treasury, Dept. of (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Unemployment Compensation Commission (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Unemployment Compensation Commission, Miners (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1954-1955 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1957 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Virginia State Bar (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Virginia State Ports Authority, 1954 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Virginia State Ports Authority, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Virginia State Ports Authority, 1956 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Virginia State Ports Authority, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Virginia State Library (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Virginia State Library, Land Officer (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Virginia State Library, Board (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, Board of Trustees (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, State employees (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Restoration of Citizenship, 1954-1958 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Convict Road Camp (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, State Board of (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, State Board of, Prison Labor (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, State Board of, Recommendations (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, State Board of, Southampton Farm (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, State Board of, State Farm for Defective Misdemeanors (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, State Board of, The Penitentiary (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, State Board of, Virginia Industrial Farm for Women (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, Director of Welfare and Institutions, 1954 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, Director of Welfare and Institutions, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, Director of Welfare and Institutions, 1956 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, Director of Welfare and Institutions, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, Electrocutions (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, Electrocutions, Lloyd Junius Dobie (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, Electrocutions, Sterling Groome (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, Electrocutions, Alonzo Russell (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, Parole Board (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, Public Welfare, 1954 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, Public Welfare, 1955 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, Public Welfare, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, Public Welfare, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, Public Welfare, Juvenile Criminals (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, Public Welfare, State Board of (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, Corrections, Public Welfare, Virginia Industrial School for Boys (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Series II: Judicial, 1954-1958., Extent: 1.4 cu. ft. (4 boxes). (Box Boxes 57-60)
  The Judicial records are housed in 4 boxes and are arranged by Court.
  - Attorney General, 1954 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Attorney General, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Attorney General, 1956 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Attorney General, 1957 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Attorney General, Estate of Granville P. Meade (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Attorney General, Veterans War Claims, 1954-1957 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Attorney General, Motion Picture Board of Censors (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Judges, Elections, 1954-1957 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Circuit Courts, 9th Judicial Circuit, C. Champion Bowles (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Circuit Courts, 9th Judicial Circuit, Miscellaneous (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Circuit Courts, 10th Judicial Circuit (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Circuit Courts, 10th Judicial Circuit, Miscellaneous (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Circuit Courts, 12th Judicial Circuit (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Circuit Courts, 13th Judicial Circuit (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Circuit Courts, 17th Judicial Circuit (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Circuit Courts, 18th Judicial Circuit (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Circuit Courts, 21st Judicial Circuit (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Circuit Courts, 21st Judicial Circuit, Recommendations (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Circuit Courts, 23rd Judicial Circuit (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Circuit Courts, 24th Judicial Circuit (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Circuit Courts, 26th Judicial Circuit (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Circuit Courts, 29th Judicial Circuit (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Circuit Courts, 33rd Judicial Circuit (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Circuit Courts, 35th Judicial Circuit (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Circuit Courts, 36th Judicial Circuit (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Corporation Courts, City of Charlottesville (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Corporation Courts, City of Norfolk (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Corporation Courts, South Norfolk, Undated (Box 59, Folder 1-2)
  - Corporation Courts, South Norfolk, Vernon P. Forehand (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Corporation Courts, South Norfolk, Robert E. Gibson (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Corporation Courts, South Norfolk, J.B. Bray, Jr. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Hustings Court, City of Richmond (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Law and Equity Court, City of Richmond (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Supreme Court of Appeals, 1954-1957 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Supreme Court of Appeals, Phillip H. Burcher (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Supreme Court of Appeals, Robert L. Hicks (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Supreme Court of Appeals, Retirement, 1954-1957 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Series III: General Assembly, 1954-1958., Extent: 2.8 cu. ft. (8 boxes). (Box Boxes 61-68)
  The General Assembly records are housed in 8 boxes and are arranged by General Assembly session with subjects interfiled by session. Records include: notes on bills, Commissions, extra sessions of 1955 and 1956 and Virginia Advisory Legislative Council.
  - Subseries A: 1954
    - January-February (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - March (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - April-December (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - House (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - House, Notes on Bills (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Legislature (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Legislature, Bills Signed by Governor (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Senate (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Senate, Notes on Bills (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Teacher's salaries (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Williamsburg, Convening of Joint Assembly in Colonial Capitol (Box 62, Folder 5-6)
    - Commission on Forest Resources, SJR 22 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Commission to Study Cerebral Palsied (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Commission to Study Juvenile Delinquency (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Commission to Study Treatment of Alcoholics (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Commission on Special Education (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Jamestown Commission (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Rochambeau Road Committee (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Virginia World War II Memorial Commission (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Subseries B: 1955
    - House (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - House, Extra Session (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - House, Extra Session, Bills signed by the Governor (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - House, Extra Session, Messages (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Senate (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Senate, Extra Session (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Subseries C: 1956
    - January-February (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - March-April (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - May-November (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Williamsburg, Convening in Colonial Capitol (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - House (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - House, Notes on Bills (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Legislature (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Legislature, Bills signed by the Governor (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Legislature, Messages (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Senate (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Senate, Notes on Bills (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Extra Session, January-June (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Extra Session, July-December (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Extra Session, House, Notes on Bills (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Extra Session, Legislature, Bills signed by Governor (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Extra Session, Legislature, Messages (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Extra Session, Senate, Notes on Bills (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Extra Session, Special Attention (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Extra Session, Mansion Luncheons (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Extra Session, Mental Hospitals (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Extra Session, Model (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Extra Session, Motor Fuel Tax (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Extra Session, Norfolk Division, William and Mary 4 year program (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Extra Session, Northern Virginia University Center (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Extra Session, Retarded Children (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Extra Session, Sales Tax (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Extra Session, Tuberculosis (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Extra Session, Whitehead (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Subseries D: 1958
    - Legislature (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Advisory Legislative Council (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Series IV General Correspondence:, 1954-1958., Extent: 19.95 cu. ft. (57 boxes). (Box Boxes 68-124)
  The General Correspondence are housed in 57 boxes and are arranged alphabetically by subject. Notable subjects include: Civil Rights, Constitutional Convention of 1956, Federal versus State Responsibility, Jamestown Celebration - 350th Anniversary, Proclamations, Requests, Segregation (including Little Rock, Arkansas situation, integration and interposition), Southern Governors, Governor's Speeches, Statements, States Rights, and Taxes.
  - Airlines (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - American Association of University Women (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - American Cancer Society (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - American Heritage Foundation (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - American Korean Foundation (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - American Legion (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - American Red Cross (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Anti-Litterbug Council (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Anti-Tornado Conference, Miscellaneous (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Appointments with Governor, 1954-1955 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Appointments with Governor, 1956-1957 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Astor, Lady Nancy (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Atomic Energy (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Automotive Trade Association (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Benjamin Franklin 250th Anniversary (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Bill of Rights (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Bonds of Israel (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Booker T. Washington, Birthplace Memorial (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Boy Scouts of America (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Breaks Interstate Park Committee (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Brotherhood (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Cape Henry (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Capitol, State (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Care (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Carwile, Howard H. (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Celebrations (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Misc. (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Junior (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Chamber of Commerce, United States (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Virginia (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Christian Children's Fund, Inc. (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Civil rights (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Colonial Williamsburg (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Colonial Williamsburg, Removal of Eastern State (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Commission issued, 1954 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Commission issued, 1955 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Commission issued, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Commission issued, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Commission, Propaganda (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Community fund (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Constitution of the United States (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Constitution Convention, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Council of State government (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Crusade for Freedom (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Daylight Saving Time (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Defenders of Sovereignty and Individual Liberties (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Delegated Designated by the Governor, 1954 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Delegated Designated by the Governor, 1955 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Delegated Designated by the Governor, 1956 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Delegated Designated by the Governor, 1957 January-June (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Delegated Designated by the Governor, 1957 July-December (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Democratic State Central Committee (Box 73, Folder 4-5)
  - Democratic Convention, Virginia, 1956 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Development Committee of the Virginia Safety Association (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Elections, Special (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Elections, Writs of (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Election Statistics (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Employment Service (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Escheat (Box 74, Folder 7-8)
  - Federal Aid to Schools (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Federal Housing Administration (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Federal Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Federal Legislation, 1954 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Federal Legislation, 1955 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Federal Legislation, 1956-1957 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Federal Security (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Federal versus State responsibility (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Federation of Women's Clubs (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Fines (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Fire prevention (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Fire protection, Southeastern States Compact Commission (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Floods (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Foreign correspondence (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Gambling (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - General Lee's Birthday Celebration (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Goshen Pass (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Governor Stanley's Inauguration (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Governors of other states, 1953-1954 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Governors of other states, 1955 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Governors of other states (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Conference, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Conference, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Conference, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Conference, 1956, Highways (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Conference, 1957 January-April (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Governor's Conference, 1957 May-June (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Conference, 1957 July-December (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Conference, 1957, Supplemental (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Conference, 1958 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Conference, 1954, New York (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Governor's Conference, 1955, Chicago (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Conference, 1955, New York (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Conference, 1955, White House (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Griffenhagen, Surveys (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Guston Hall, Regents (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Hampton Roads, Maritime exchange (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Hobby (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Holiday information (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Holiday, Legal (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Home for Needy Confederate Women (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Indians (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Inter-agency Committee on Recreation (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Intergovernmental Relations Commission (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Interstate Oil Compact Commission (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Izaak Walton League (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Jamestown Celebration, 1953-1955 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Jamestown Celebration, 1956 January-June (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Jamestown Celebration, 1956 July-December (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Jamestown Celebration, 1957 January-March (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Jamestown Celebration, 1957 April-June (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Jamestown Celebration, 1957 July-September (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Jamestown Celebration, 1957 October-December (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - John Marshall Celebration (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Juveniles (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Kellam, Sidney (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Korean Foundation (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Labor, Right to work law (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Law enforcement (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - League of Municipalities (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Legal matters (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Legislation, Misc. (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Action, Requests for (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Letters of Commendation, Governor's Office (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Letters of Congratulations (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Letters of endorsement (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Letters of greeting and welcome (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Letters of introductions, To and from the Governor (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Letters of recommendation (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Letters returned (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Letters to department heads (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - License (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Local affairs (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Lottery (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Lynchings (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - March of Dimes (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Mariners Museum (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Miller School Board of Trustees (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Mother's Day (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Mount Vernon, Board of Visitors (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Music (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - National Capitol Park and Planning Commission (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - National Capitol Regional Planning Council (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - National Democratic Committee, Proposal to amend Cannon's (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - National Democratic Convention (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - National Education Association (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - National Employment of the physically handicapped (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - National Employ the Handicapped Week (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - National Freedom Day (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - National Rivers and Harbors Committee (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - National Safety Council (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - National Society of the Daughters of the American Revolution (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Notaries, Misc. (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Notaries, Resignations (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Oddity (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Old appointment sheets (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Opinions of the Attorney General (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - People to People Foundation (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Permissions granted (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Photographs (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Political matters (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - President's Highway Safety Conference (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Press, 1954 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Press, 1955 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Press, 1955-1957 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Proclamations (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Proclamations data, 1954 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Proclamations data, 1955 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Proclamations data, 1956 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Proclamations data, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Proclamations, Extra copies (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Queen Elizabeth II (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Queen Mother, Visit of (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Racial (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Radio broadcasts (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Radio W.R.N.L. (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Radio W.R.V.A. (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Reciprocity board (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Recommendations, Misc. (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Referendum, Constitutional Convention (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Religious worship (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Rent problems (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Report, Secretary of the Commonwealth (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Requests, 1954 January-October (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - REquests, 1954 July-October (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Requests, 1954 November-December (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Requests, 1955 January-March (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Requests, 1955 April-June (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Requests, 1955 July-December (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Requests, 1955 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Requests, 1956 January-June (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Requests, 1956 July-December (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Requests, 1957 January-March (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Requests, 1957 April-June (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Requests, 1957 July-September (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Requests, 1957 October-December (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Requests, Constitutions (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Requests, Flags (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Resolutions (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Richmond, City of (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac Railroad Investments (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Richmond Memorial Hospital (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Right to Work Law (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Safety, 1954 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Safety, 1955 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Safety, 1956 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Safety, 1957 January-June (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Safety, 1957 July-December (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Safety, Governor's Plan (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Salem Church Dam Project (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Segregation, 1954 January-April (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Segregation, 1954 May (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Segregation, 1954 June (Box 100, Folder 1-2)
  - Segregation, 1954 June (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Segregation, 1954 July (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Segregation, 1954 August-September (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Segregation, 1954 September-October (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Segregation, 1954 November-December (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Segregation, Commission to Study Schools (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Segregation, 1955 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Segregation, 1955 January-June (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Segregation, 1955 July-December (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Segregation, 1956 January (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Segregation, 1956 February (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Segregation, 1956 March-May (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Segregation, 1956 June-July (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Segregation, 1956 August (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Segregation, 1956 September-October (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Segregation, 1955-1956 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Segregation, 1957 January-June (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Segregation, 1957 July-September (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Segregation, 1957 October-December (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Segregation, Little Rock, Arkansas, situation (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Segregation, Petition (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Segregation, Copies, Segregation REsolutions sent to Study Commission (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Segregation, Correspondence (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Segregation, Withholding Plan, 1956 July (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Segregation, Withholding Plan, 1956 August (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Segregation, Withholding Plan, 1956 September-October (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Segregation, Governor's Speeches (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Segregation, Wall, J. Barrye (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Segregation, Integration, "Let My People Go" (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Segregation, Integration, 1954 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Segregation, Pro-Integration, 1955 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Segregation, Pro-Integration, 1956 (Box 110, Folder 4)